Go ahead. Make that nightmare of yours come true.
I'm Baku Yorozu.
I'm an agent for the
Secret Defense Organization, CODE.
My mission... to eradicate evil.
At least, that's what I dream about every night.
I'm actually a pretty normal guy.
Tonight's mission:
Stop the bomber.
But...
For some reason, I'm the one being chased?!
Hey you! Stop right there!
You won't get away!
Why is this what I'm dreaming about?!
Good luck.
Hey!
Code number: 7.
Good night to you!
Nem!
Good night.
CASE 2: EXPLODE
For some reason, I'm being chased.
Oh! That's it!
My mission must be to protect you,
our national star.
It must be tough, huh?
Having to play secret agent
even in your dreams...
It's nothing.
Wait!
You know this is a dream?
Yes.  But I just take in my surroundings, and play my role accordingly!
Nem, you're a diabolical one.
Anyway...
Watch the O as it becomes a 3!
OK!
Close the 3 again and
buddy, you're busted!
What?!
Wanted criminal Baku Yorozu,
you're under arrest.
Why are you arresting me?!
Because the role I'm playing is...
Police Chief for a Day!
It's that monster again.
I'm gonna blow everything up.
I see now.
So you're the bomber.
Oh right, cuffed.
Nem, take it off!
I can't do that as an officer of the law..!
No, you've gotta!
IMPACT
Woah, you're a useful little thing.
Stop the bomber...
That's my mission.
IMPACT
MEZTZAMERO! MEZTZAMERO!
I'm on it.
Transform!
GOOD MORNING! RIDER!
Z-ZEZ-ZEZTZ!
IMPACT
Whoops!
You can't stop this nightmare!
No way, no way, no way, no way!
Hey! Did you cause that blast?!
Get him!
No! No, no, no, no, no!
The heck was with that dream?
Something's weird here.
I can usually control my lucid dreams.
This weird thing I was wearing
in a dream the other day
was still on me when I woke up,
for some reason.
Transform!
Wait... Maybe I can transform in real life, too?
I'll put this on...
TOKYO METROPOLITAN POLICE DEPARTMENT
TOKYO PUBLIC SECURITY COMMITTEE
PARANORMAL AFFAIRS DIVISION
I'm already on the outside looking in...
I'm this young and I'm being demoted...?
No. It's not possible.
I'm a competent woman.
Ow...
GOOD MORNING, CHIEF FUJIMI!
Morning.
I'm impressed you made it, Nasuka.
Only my parents can call me by my first name.
Sir, have you been here all night?
Yeah.
CLASSIFIED
You're still looking into Baku Yorozu?
Sit down, will ya.
Yes, sir.
C'mon, we're leaving. Get ready.
Huh? Wait, where to?!
If Baku Yorozu met a Nightmare,
he might be about to commit a violent crime.
There's no scientific basis for that.
Yes, there is!
His injury from two days ago healed so fast, they cut him loose yesterday.
These circumstances are clearly inexplicable.
This is a Black Case.
He's hiding something.
Real suspicious.
Is it really?
HIIISSS!
Pretty sure "Meow" would've worked better.
Hiss!
Mr. Baku Yorozu?
What?
What the—?! You're...!
MPD, Fujimi...
And Nagumo.
Sorry to bother you so soon
after your discharge,
but please accompany us to the station.
Huh, why?!
We can't force you to come.
My dream's coming true.
You're arresting me! I'm a wanted man!
No, neither of those things is the case.
What do you have hiding there?
I'm not so sure, myself...
I saw it in my dream, and
I woke up with it, for some reason.
Do you remember what the dream was about?!
Yeah. I ran into Nem...
Nem?
Yeah.
So what?!
She appears in everyone's dreams, you know!
Mine as well.
No, that wasn't all!
Suddenly, a demon-looking thing suddenly appeared...
Did you...
Did you meet a Nightmare?
- A Nightmare?
- Yes.
You mean... that monster?!
Yes!
Tell me everything!
What was the dream like?!
Was that a Nightmare?!
Tone it down, sir, or I'll arrest you.
One shot a gun at me,
one blew up a bunch of police cars...
Impossible.
That's the same dream I had yesterday!
What? You did?
The same dream! The same dream!
The same! The same dream!
The same dream!
Different people having the same dream...
It's completely inexplicable, a Black Case!
A Black Case?
The Paranormal Affairs Division deals with unsolved cases that seem logically inexplicable.
And... I suspect the Nightmares are behind them.
- The Nightmares?!
- Yes.
Nasuka. The case files.
They're classified, he's not authorized, and there's no scientifi...
Just hand them over.
Nightmares are monsters that appear in your dreams when you're sleeping.
We don't know how they appear or what it is they're after.
What we do know...
is that they force people to have bad dreams.
That doesn't mean anything.
Sometimes dreams are like that!
These aren't just dreams.
What you're describing is the purview
of urban legends and occult magazines.
Our duty as police officers is to solve crimes that actually happen!
Becoming a police officer was my dream.
What?
I want to believe in my duty...
In the mission
of the Paranormal Affairs Division.
Totally a demotion...
I've been demoted...
The police?!
What have you gotten yourself into this time?
Nothing, nothing! They just
had some questions about a case.
Oh, well. I guess that's
a one-in-a-hundred thing.
Unlucky you.
Guess so.
So heavy.
Hey, Minami. Have you ever had
the same dream as someone else?
What? Don't be ridiculous.
Yeah, I figured...
But the thing about dreams is...
They say that they're a manifestation of a person's subconscious.
They're a world that you've created.
A world only you can see!
Fair enough.
What's wrong?
- What is it?
- Stay back!
You just helped me by carrying our groceries.
Something's gonna happe... No, stay back!
Could be a meteorite or an explosion, I just really don't wanna be a part of that.
You drama queen. I'm leaving.
It might happen, though!
I stepped in poo!
I warned you!
What do I do?!
- Wash it off! Wash it off.
- Wash this?!
- I'll take this and head back home first.
- Wait, what?!
- Please! Stay back! Go away!
- You're just gonna leave me?!
Man!
I'm so curious, I can't sleep!
Who's calling me?
Are you going to abandon your duties?
I'm afraid I don't understand
what you're saying.
My dream self understands
English, but I don't.
...Okay.
I asked if you're going to abandon your duties?
Excuse me. May I ask who you're trying to reach?
Code number: 7.
Wait a minute.
I thought I was only a secret agent in my dreams.
I'm sure as heck wide awake right now!
Open the closet door.
The voice is coming from here?
Huh?
What's this thing?
Hey, my clothes!
Huh?
HUH?!
What is this place?
This is a control center
we've prepared for you.
We'd like you to take on missions
as one of our agents.
Zero?
Where's that voice coming from?
It's me.
Zero, you're a robot?!
No, I'm being controlled remotely.
Wait, hang on!
Am I really a secret agent now?!
With enough faith
your dreams can come true.
You have one duty.
Infiltrate the dreams of others,
and stop the Nightmares' bad dreams
before they come to pass.
I will be supporting your
operations in the field.
These items contain the power
to make dreams come true.
Give it a spin.
Here goes...
What's this thing?
Here.
"Transform. The power
to change your body's shape."
It should be useful on your mission.
Wait a minute.
Zero, you just said... I have to stop the Nightmares'
bad dreams before they come to pass.
Indeed.
When a Nightmare gives a Dreamer
their ultimate bad dream,
the Dreamer becomes locked away
in darkness, never to awaken again.
Never to awaken...?
Because the Nightmare will
have taken over their body.
Wait.
Then I'll have to stop the bomber, or else the Dreamer will...
Wait a minute!
What was that thing you said before?!
With enough faith...
No, after that!
You have one duty.
Infiltrate the dreams of others...
Yeah, that part!
Impossible.
That's the same dream I had yesterday!
That was...
Mr. Fujimi's dream...?
It appears the bomber
has hijacked a police van.
I've gotta stop the Bomber or else Mr. Fuijimi will be in danger...!
I'm ready.
Zero!
You can enter my dreams, too?!
Of course.
Come on. Let's stop the bomber.
Vroom... Vrvrvrooommm!
Why am I getting on your back?!
Ah, it's just a witty joke.
IMPACT
MEZTZAMERO!
Transform!
GOOD MORNING! RIDER!
Z-ZEZ-ZEZTZ!
I'll carry out my mission.
Not bad.
OMI POLICE STATION
He's after the police precinct?!
TRANSFORM
GOOD MORNING! RIDER!
Z-ZEZ-ZEZTZ!
TRANSFORM
Use this weapon.
SWORD MODE
If I eliminate you, I save Mr. Fujimi, right?
Dreams...
are a reflection of the Dreamer's subconscious.
Who's there?!
Dreams...
are the refuge of wishes left
ungranted in the real world.
The Dreamer's subconscious...
When the Mind's Door is opened,
the nightmare will begin.
It can't be...
The person wishing
for this bomber nightmare...
is the Dreamer, Mr. Fujimi, himself?
Why, Mr. Fujimi?
Next time on Kamen Rider Zeztz:
You must find the Mind's Doors
somewhere in the dream world.
What have I been doing up until now...?
I want to protect Mr. Fujimi's dream.
The only one who can do that, is Zeztz.
I've made your dream come true.
Where are you?! You Nightmare?!
O' world, awaken to a nightmare!
If we don’t hurry and stop the Nightmares, the world will end.
Stop the bomber...
I'll carry out my mission!
CASE 3: ERODE