It turned out that Glotta was the
one who took Comel from me.
Dente's death was also on her.
I had lost myself in anger, but his final words to me brought me back to my senses.
Helping Shouma protect humans and topple Stomach Inc. will make up for Comel's sins.
With that resolve embedded,
we defeated Glotta, once and for all.
Glotta-neesan's gone as well...?
Like she was rushing to be, if anything.
They managed to best Lango-niisan.
She was never going to win.
How unfortunate...
I wanted to get to know her better...
Apologies for the wait, my friends.
What did you want to tell us?
I've been considering how we could
mass produce Dark Treats-
Turning the entire human world into a ranch ran through my head.
What do you think?
...your reasons?
Having to inject joy then quietly kidnap them one-by-one takes far too long.
As such, overtaking their world-
to have a full supply of human livestock at our fingertips would be far more convenient.
Wonderful! I love it, Papa!
But sir, with the Granute hunters still there, overtaking their entire world is-
Perhaps you could make this work?
Aaaand that...
- I'm done!
- Thank you.
You've been coming a lot, lately.
Not eating just snacks, I hope?
I'm eating lots of proper meals, too. Don't worry.
Good. Glad to hear it.
My younger sister was often scolded
for eating nothing but snacks.
She must've loved snacking
as much as I do, huh?
Here.
I gotta snack tons to use you, after all.
What's he doing?
Glasses Creeping Closer
‎
Me too! I saw people acting all weird.
Eh, you did?
Yeah. Someone was riding a slide repeatedly.
Another was stroking a postbox non-stop.
I just passed it off as them having fun and praying for some prize.
But it's definitely weird,
now that we're comparing notes.
Mind if I go check things out, after?
People aren't going missing, but still.
Go for it. I'll have a look around myself.
Thanks. Let's have lunch first, though.
That looks yum! Thanks.
- Your favourite soba's on the menu, today.
- Don't mind if I do, then!
"Inoue"
Hello? Inoue-san?
Out, I guess?
I'd recommend trying his store in the daytime, if you're looking for him.
His store?
Could you tell me where it is?
Don't you reckon Stomach's
part-timers have been quiet?
But I guess that's to be expected with Lango and Glotta out of the picture.
Still, it's the longest we've gone not sniffing any out since I first got here.
The new CEO's tired of Dark Treats...
would be too optimistic of a take, probably.
My teeth...!
A Granute?
No...
I'm gonna eat this rock...!
Lakia?
Oi.
Give that back! I need to eat my rock!
Why that rock?!
Rock... Rock... Rock!
You're gonna kill your teeth!
Lakia, what's going on?!
Shouma?
Check this guy's belly!
He's not a Granute, right?
Give me my rock!
He's human!
I want to eat my rock! My rock! My rock!
My teeth!
- Don't worry, we'll have that looked that soon.
- I want my rock! My rock!
Thanks for this!
Thanks, Sachika-san.
You saved us big time.
Don't mention it.
If this stuff's still going on, then...
Yeah. Something's definitely up.
Push those buttons.
That more or less clears simple commands.
Not bad for a first trial, I suppose.
President Bocca's a more dangerous
fellow than I anticipated.
Perhaps you could make this work?
Papa, isn't that-
The corpse of a certain Granute.
But why have you brought it?
He possessed a particularly unique ability.
One that I wanted to keep within arm's reach to exploit, some day.
And that ability was...?
Something akin to hypnosis.
He could control the actions of others.
Just a tad, mind you.
Heh? A Granute like that existed?
I would've loved to meet him.
I suggest we bring humans under
our control with this ability.
That would simplify the manufacturing of Dark Treats, wouldn't you say, Nyelv-kun?
You poor thing.
Vying for Bocca's seat got you assassinated and exploited even after death.
Though, I really shouldn't be judging.
Snacks Cafe Hidamari?
Why does that sound familiar?
- Hi.
- Welcome.
It's a snacks cafe called "Hidamari".
Right, this is Shouma's usual spot?
Ahh, Shouma-kun's friend from the other day?
My name's Karakida Hanto.
I'm a freelance writer.
Here.
Are you...Inoue Masaru-san?
Yes. I don't remember introducing myself?
Actually, I'm looking into some
unsolved missing-persons cases.
Did a family member of yours go missing around twenty years ago?
Yes, actually...
It was my little sister, Michiru.
Inoue Michiru-san?
Wait, did you discover what happened?!
Did you find a lead-
I'm sorry.
I've...just been asking around
about that same name...
I see.
My apologies.
Another one.
This person's sister's was outside doing a handstand for four hours-
before her arms gave way and they dragged her home.
Do you know where?
Mmm...based on other sightings of her...
The intersection at Moriyachou's
second district, I think?
Moriyachou, second district...
There it is.
The sightings seem to be concentrated around here, at the moment.
One other thing caught my eye.
Some shady guy in a black hood keeps popping up near those spots, apparently.
People online are wondering if its a Granute.
I think I also...
They might be on to something.
Let's look for that guy around here.
- Be right back.
- Take care!
This was her, from around that time.
She'd left for her university classes
that day, but never came back.
She didn't flee from home, I'm guessing?
The police asked the same, but I can't
think of any reason she would have.
She had plans with friends at
a dessert buffet the next day.
You should have seen how excited she was.
She had a sweet tooth, I take it?
She loved snacking in general, not just sweets.
Quite gluttonous too, I might add.
She even joined a snacks circle in her uni.
Yum! It's sweet yet salty, and also springy!
Michiru's still alive out there...
Our parents and I continued to hold onto that hope...
But the anxiety ate away at them, and they passed away soon after...
I'm all that's left of our family.
This Inoue Michiru has the greatest resemblence to Shouma's mum, so far.
Could I...take a picture of this?
I won't spread it or anything.
Of course. If it helps your search.
Thank you.
"Inoue Shouma"
Sorry, one sec.
What's up?
Huh?
Alright, I'll head over.
Sorry, something's come up.
I might drop by again.
Let me know if you find anything.
Of course.
Did you...ever tell Shouma about
what happened to your sister?
I haven't- nor to any of my other customers.
I see.
Thank you for your time.
Please excuse me.
Take care.
What now...
Should I tell Shouma about this?
Thanks. But I think I'm still too afraid.
He's already friends with Masaru-san.
That's probably a good reason keep a lid on it.
What should I do...
It's my fault they're dead...
It's my fault the Stomach family is crumbling...!
What do I do? What do I do, Shiita!?
Help me...!
What's wrong? Not taking Shiita's appearance?
If I wanted to dress up as Shiita...
I'd have to stick her in this black Gavv!
It's disgusting! I don't want that!
Really?
I think it's adorable!
Hey Lizel, am I really on the right track?
All I wanted was vengeance for Shiita-
and to get back a little at Lango-niisan...
But now he and Glotta-neesan
are dead, because of me...
on top of my Gavv becoming this...
The future I had in mind is getting further away...
I'm scared...
A lot's changed, and it's shaken you up.
Things will be fine. You still have me!
Lango and Glotta got what was coming to them.
Don't blame yourself for that!
You just need to keep on keeping on!
I want to get stronger.
Then let's start by giving
that Gavv a little clean!
- Go check over there.
- 'Kay.
Lakia!
Dance.
So this was his doing.
Stop!
Shady freak.
Show me that face!
Suga!?
You've got some balls getting
up to this crap again...!
What is it now!?
What are you planning!?
There's nothing going on in his head.
Hanto!
Nyelv.
He's not the Suga-san you remember. Not anymore.
He's just a mindless marionette of mine, now.
That body...
Did you modify him as well?!
I picked him up after you
lot beat him down,
and kept him alive, thinking I could use him,
until I obtained a peculiar
Granute's corpse, recently.
So I used him as a lab rat.
That's vile...
I'd agree.
His body actually gave out and died when I was splicing the black Gavv on-
turning him into a nice obedient zombie.
But Suga-san was all about making the
ultimate life form, so it works out for him.
Now it's adding up.
Doing this to Suga-san,
and those people acting strangely-
were experiments to control humans.
What's the next step!?
True. What could it be?
People's lives aren't your toys!
Prepare yourself, Nyelv!
VRASTUMGEAR!
- What a smart-ass!
- Let's make him pay!
FRAPPÉ ON!
MASTER!
DESSERT ON!
DISH UP!
MAKING! MAKING! SWEETS MAKING!
Henshin!
FRAPPÉ CUSTOM! SLUSHY SLUSHY!
À LA MODE MODE! BON APPÉTIT!
MASTER TASTE!
Open up, Suga-san.
COOKIE!
BITE COOKIE!
Henshin.
BREACOOKIE! YUMMY!
Suga's even stronger than before!
I did fiddle with him.
By the way, those explode.
Over here, Suga-san!
- Ready, and-
- Let go!
Gavv and Vram are your enemies.
Bastard... You're trying to puppet me as well?!
Not happening!!
I decide what I do!!
Destroy Gavv and Vram.
SWEETS TIME!
Nyelv!
Like my poison swamp?
It still affects you despite your
current strength, thankfully.
This is all my natural ability amounts to,
unlike our older brother.
How bitter.
CHOCO! SNAP & CRACK!
Hanto!?
What are you doing!?
Nyelv's over there!
They must've taken control of Hanto
like they did those people!
Time to go, Suga-san.
FROZEN!
Next time on Kamen Rider Gavv:
Stop, Hanto!
Must be Nyelv's handiwork.
You're seriously following Suga's orders?
Human lives and hearts aren't
for you to experiment with!
You better be ready!
At the End of Broken Feelings
‎